HELLO, TWENTY - WONHEE
ULTIMATE VIBE CENTRAL
MANGWON-DONG
LIVELY STREETS WITH ENERGETIC YOUNG PEOPLE
Hello, everyone.
This is the seventh episode
of Hello, Twenty - Wonhee.
I'm looking forward to the new experience
I'll have with today's guest.
We're in Mangwon-dong today.
What's going on?
Have you ever been here?
I think just once outside of work.
Here in Mangwon-dong,
you're about to embark on a journey
of self-discovery.
Self-discovery? Well, here I am.
Sorry.
QUICK APOLOGY
WE START TO FIND OURSELVES AT 20
FIRST STEP IN SELF-DISCOVERY:
DEVELOP YOUR OWN TASTE
SEVENTH ITEM ON WONHEE'S BUCKET LIST
FIGURE OUT MY TASTE
We prepared a questionnaire for you.
- A questionnaire?
- Here you go.
- I see.
- Your goal today is
figuring out who you are as a person.
An all-rounder guide is waiting for you.
Is she who I'm thinking of?
The multi-faceted entertainer.
- Shall we go meet her?
- Sure.
I've been dying to meet her.
My group members and I
are all huge fans of hers.
I can't wait to learn
how to crack jokes from her.
I hope to learn as much as I can
from our amazing girlie today.
I'll see you soon, girlie.
MEETUP SPOT:
A VINTAGE SHOP IN MANGWON-DONG
3 SECONDS AWAY
I've wanted to visit this place.
"An invitation to happiness."
- Hello.
- Gosh, hello.
EPISODE 7 GIRLIE
YOUTUBER CHARLES
Am I watching YouTube?
- Nice to meet you.
SHY AT FIRST MEETING
Can I call you by your first name?
Of course, Ms. Wonhee.
Speak casually, Charles.
- May I?
- Sure.
CASUAL TONE, FORMAL GESTURE
Thanks.
You can talk casually, too.
Let's both speak casually.
Okay, I'd love that.
COMPLETELY DISARMED
Let's both talk casually.
- Shall we?
- Sure.
All right.
- Starting now, okay?
- Okay.
Whoever talks formally
performs a party trick as a penalty.
I don't have any.
Then make one up, Ms. Charles.
OH, NO
A PENALTY IN JUST 5 SECONDS
Show me your party trick.
NOSTRIL FLARING
I can do something similar.
NOSTRIL COLLAPSING
NOSTRIL PARTY TRICK
I can do it, too.
SQUEEZES NOSTRILS SHUT
Wait, but...
NOSTRIL TRICKS GALORE
Can you move your nose like this?
Your nose, not your upper lip.
Your nose, not your nostrils.
- I can't do that.
- Great, mine's unique.
What brings you here?
I'm here to shoot an episode with you.
Well, it's a date.
Why did you ask me here?
It's the perfect place
to figure out what you like.
That's a good choice.
I don't really know my own taste.
- Did you just read off the script?
- No.
IT'S A QUESTIONNAIRE
I don't have a set taste yet.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Don't you like digicams?
- Yes, I do.
On your Instagram--
The moment I walked in,
these digicams caught my eye.
- I've had my eyes on it, too.
- Really?
- Let's settle it with a game.
- Right.
- Are you paying for everything?
- Sure.
Then you're the boss.
Want to call me "boss"?
Yes, boss.
By the way,
- you're so pretty.
- What on earth?
Seriously, you're so cute.
THAT'S TOO MUCH
My gosh. Sorry about that.
I rarely see someone as pretty as you.
Don't you ever check the mirror?
ON ANOTHER LEVEL
- You're something else.
- I'm an idol.
NATURAL AT HYPING PEOPLE UP
What's on that board?
My assignment for the day.
It's a questionnaire
to help me find what I like.
- So many questions, right?
- We can go through them together.
Let's figure out your taste.
LIGHT AND CHEERFUL
LOUD AND BOISTEROUS
SAME WORDS, DIFFERENT VIBES
Oh, no. We're doomed.
- Sorry, we're good.
- Take it back.
I will. Let's have a look around.
Oh, this one is a film camera.
- They are mock-ups.
- Digicams are easier to use.
These are the real things.
- That's a film camera.
- Really?
- Is this the only digicam?
- Yes.
OOPS
Let's have a look around.
BATTLE DELAYED
Glasses are great, too.
- Shall we try some on?
- The glasses?
Totally my dad's vibe.
RETRO VIBES
I think these are prescription glasses.
This pair, too. What in the world?
MAXIMUM HIPSTER ENERGY
Is it okay to sell these?
Don't you feel dizzy?
- Just yesterday...
- Try this on.
BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL
I can't see properly.
Have you considered LASIK?
I won't be able to wear contacts then,
but they're a must for performers.
I can't risk looking too plain on stage.
WHO COULD'VE GUESSED?
I'm already worried because my features
are too soft for an idol.
That's nonsense.
- It's the truth.
- Really?
Jeez, haven't you seen other idols?
UNFILTERED HONESTY
- You're so funny.
- My features aren't strong.
She's got an amazing personality.
HEHE
- That looks nice.
- Really?
- Yes, I dig the geek-chic vibe.
- Geek chic?
- Get that pair.
- Should I?
Don't I remind you of someone
in this outfit?
You know, Mr. Long Legs.
AIR GUITAR
GOING ABOVE AND BEYOND
I'm sorry. I'll try to pull my weight.
WONHEE'S WORK ETHIC
IS GIVING US A WAKEUP CALL
I'm an ISFP who tries hard to be outgoing.
My best friend is an ISFP, too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The goofball you met earlier
is the real me.
WONHEE'S FIRST IMPRESSION
Can you move your nose like this?
ISFP'S MIND IS AN ENIGMA
I was nervous about meeting you
because I wanted to make you laugh.
- Really?
- I wanted to make sure you had fun.
- I'm having fun.
- Really? I'm so glad.
- Let's check out the clothes.
- Okay.
Do you have a signature style now?
Not really.
- What kind of style do you like?
- I'm into unique vintage pieces.
But I don't want old-fashioned stuff.
Let's see.
For example, I'd like this better
without the floral pattern.
- This?
- This much is good.
I like sparkly vintage pieces
with a unique charm like...
Wait, this is so pretty.
- Do you think this jacket is for sale?
- I think so.
- I like it.
- Want to take it off?
MANNEQUIN'S ARMS ARE BARE
Too revealing.
Like this...
- Wear that to the airport.
- To the airport?
- It'd be perfect.
- You think so?
Wow, it's really nice.
CHECKS THE MIRROR
How do I look?
- Simply stunning.
- Really?
STARES
Does it suit me?
This is sick.
UNFILTERED THOUGHTS
You're so pretty.
- Thanks.
- What's it like being you?
When I look at my reflection after makeup,
I feel guilty because I look so different.
COMPLIMENT REJECTED
I've talked about this before.
What's your favorite style?
I'm actually into quirky pieces.
How's this? It caught my eye right away.
I like it. What do you think?
- Not my thing.
- Okay.
Let's say I wore something in my video,
and people saw it elsewhere.
I want people to say,
"Hey, Charles wore that!"
It's all about being memorable.
I even wear an orange puffer jacket
to stand out.
I like clothes that really stand out.
- I've already picked one out.
- Show me. Which one is it?
Over there. This one.
INTENSE VACATION VIBES
Isn't it cute?
NOT SURE WHAT TO SAY
It is cute, but...
It's even cinched at the waist. So extra.
- I--
- But isn't that cuter?
Seriously?
SHOCKING TASTES ALL AROUND
CHECKS THE MIRROR
I want to wear this in summer.
"Charles wore this, didn't she?"
Isn't it so cute?
- I swear I'll be back.
- I'm buying this. It's so cute.
- Isn't it so cute?
- It is!
If only I were smaller...
- Won't it fit you?
- No way.
- I'm sure it will.
- I guarantee you it won't.
But it will fit.
I can prove you wrong.
Maybe not, I guess.
It's so cute, though.
- It's totally my style.
- Really?
I used to be a huge floral fan,
but I've moved on from that phase.
- You're done with it?
- I'm in my sporty era.
You are?
Isn't this too neon?
No, it's pretty.
- It's kind of wrinkly, but it's cute.
- Fair point.
The mesh looks like polka dots.
- Get it. It's so cute.
- I love polka dots.
I've never seen one like this.
You're tempting me to buy it.
It's just...
"I've never seen one like this."
That did it for me.
That's the charm of vintage items.
- Everything is special.
- Right.
- What's your shoe size?
- I'm a size 240.
- That's a surprise.
- Really?
- What about you?
- You look like a size 220.
You know what?
What a pleasant randomness.
Randomness?
What's that supposed to mean?
I've never heard of that phrase before.
Don't people usually say
"an unexpected twist"?
It was a nice surprise.
- You found it surprisingly charming?
- Yes.
I'll try to read between the lines.
CHECKING OUT ANOTHER SECTION
SWISH, SWISH
- Not our style, right?
- No.
- Let's move on.
- That's why you went quiet.
Look, that definitely meets your criteria.
What do you think?
- It's memorable.
- This dress right here
is giving Paris Fashion Week.
Wait, I've been there twice.
I think I saw this on the runway.
A SHOCKING EYE-OPENER FOR THE DESIGNERS
What do you think?
VERY PARISIAN BAKERY OWNER ENERGY
This would suit you.
So unique. Don't they have the same vibe?
ALPINE MEADOWS VIBES
I'm not sure about this.
Why not? It's cute.
Super memorable.
Why do you like this shirt
but not these dresses?
About that.
If I pair this top with simple bottoms...
- Whatever, I dig this.
- I get it now.
So one piece should be simple
- so the other can pop.
- I have a thing for patchwork, too.
- I like these little details.
- I see.
NEW KNOWLEDGE GAINED
So you like patchwork.
- This is cute.
- You really dig this style, huh?
Now, put this back.
- You have that one.
- Okay.
- Leave it.
- That's cuter, though.
IS WONHEE IN SAFE HANDS?
What about this? It's pretty cute.
- This--
- Hard pass.
But the patchwork...
I have my standards.
This is a genuine patchwork.
- This is...
- It's a fake?
QUICK TO GIVE UP
What about this?
- So?
- Is this a scarecrow?
I'd chase all the birds away.
It'd be nice not to worry about pigeons.
A HUMAN BIRD CONTROL?
VINTAGE FASHION MASTER ON RICE PADDY
This section is giving
I'm Sorry, I Love You.
What's that?
Do you really not know?
AIRED BEFORE SHE WAS BORN
I'm not good with memes.
- "Dinner with me or death?"
- I've heard of that.
- Yeah.
Lim Soo-jung wore
something like this on that show.
FINDS A NEW DRESS
This right here...
This one has that vibe.
My Lovely Sam-soon, right?
Sang-soon?
My Lovely Sam-soon.
- Haven't watched it, either.
- Really?
Jung Ryeo-won starts crying
in a similar outfit.
- She empties her bag and flops down.
- Out of the blue?
- Like this.
- Randomly?
- Holding the top?
- No, wearing it.
- Wearing it?
- In this kind of outfit.
It's giving Y2K.
So this is a true vintage clothing store.
Shall we decide on the digicam?
- There's just one.
- Exactly.
Can we take a picture with it?
Does it work?
CAMERA ON
Wait, can I take your pic?
A SHOT OF WONHEE
- Just one thing.
- Yes?
You were covering the flash.
I wondered why the photo came out orange.
So cute.
Cute, right?
Hey, it's nice.
- Rock-paper-scissors, then?
- Shall we?
- You can have it.
- Oh, shoot.
- Don't be like that.
- Okay.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
- Rock--
- Wait!
Best of three or one-off?
- One-off.
- Okay.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
WINNER, LOSER
- Is it really mine?
- Of course.
For real?
I'm a cool 20-year-old girlie.
- Thanks, Wonhee.
- No problem.
NO HESITATION IN USING THE COMPANY CARD
Lucky me.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Let's take many photos with this
to remember our day together.
Let's go to our next stop!
Let's go!
Your energy level spiked up.
POWER OF SHOPPING
- They know what they're doing here.
- Right?
They set up a photo zone.
A MUST FOR GEN Z: MIRROR SELFIE
ON TO THE NEXT DESTINATION
- It feels like I'm on Guerrilla Date.
- Right?
- Can we walk arm in arm?
- Of course.
HOLDING CLOSE
Don't people question it
- when you tell them your MBTI type?
- Like what?
They say things like,
"You can't be an ISFP."
- I'm an ENFP.
- You are?
I see.
Didn't you say you were an ISFP?
- No, I said my best friend was.
- Your best friend?
- I misheard that.
- I see.
My best friend is an ISFP.
CORRECTION
How did you get
- such an awesome personality?
- Me?
You're so chill.
Did I ever look like a horrible person?
Of course not.
- You're just 20--
- Did I?
No, I'm amazed. That's all.
You're so fun to be around,
so I want to match that energy.
To be honest,
you've thrown me off my game.
I'm struggling to keep up.
- This is a first for me.
- Right? This isn't your A game.
- It's just--
- Make me laugh.
TEASING HER
I'm dying to do that.
- You got me out of my rhythm.
- Tell me a joke.
Usually, I'm the clown of the party.
But you're making all the jokes,
so I'm at a loss.
I don't even know
what I'm supposed to be doing.
- You feel me?
- Yeah.
- I'm losing my mind.
- I'm going to run out of steam soon.
- You can pick things up then.
- Okay.
Another vintage clothing store.
Mangwon-dong is the perfect place
to discover your taste.
I'm coming back tomorrow.
I actually have a date.
With who?
WHAT'S WITH THAT ANGLE?
- Hold that up.
- With who?
Why ask, though?
You wouldn't know him.
I still want to know.
- You wouldn't know him.
- Is it a blind date?
POSSIBLE DOPAMINE RUSH DETECTED
It's not a blind date.
I'm meeting a friend.
- Anyway, I had fun shopping.
- Me too.
But the fun isn't over.
We're visiting another store.
- Really?
- This place specializes
in curated pottery and cups.
- Amazing.
- We'll shop there.
I love tomatoes.
My room is a tomato heaven
because of all the tomato-themed items.
Oh, my.
- I'm so excited.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- Gua sha!
INSTANT AMAZEMENT
FROM VARIOUS TABLEWARE
TO DELIGHTFUL HANDMADE POTTERY
CAREFULLY CURATED ITEMS
Isn't this ring so cute?
Try it on.
Help me try it.
ON TO WONHEE'S FINGER
So pretty.
- Want to buy a matching set?
- A friendship ring?
IN JUST 1 HOUR OF MEETING?
I'm getting those tomato earrings.
For now...
- Tomatoes.
I don't like them, though.
STILL IRRESISTIBLE
I like how they look.
I only eat Stevia-infused...
Gosh, check this cutie out.
- That's so cute.
- Right?
- This section is stacked.
- Yeah.
I've got plenty at home,
but I want to buy more.
- The cups--
- My gosh.
- I'm all over the place.
- Check this out!
- Dang!
- What's this?
An incense holder?
So cute.
That's so cute.
Why do they have so many cute items?
I'm going crazy.
So cute. I'm lost here.
I can't take this.
So cute. This is crazy.
My gosh!
I have to get this.
CONSUMED BY ALL THE TEMPTATION
Wait, we should look around together.
COMES TO HER SENSES
"Delicious food makes me happy."
- So relatable.
- Check this out. So cute.
I'm getting this, too.
That's so you.
That smiley face.
DELICIOUS FOOD MAKES ME HAPPY
CUTIES MAKE ME SO HAPPY
- Isn't Mangwon-dong fabulous?
- Totally.
The area is filled
with stores like this one.
I'm coming back alone.
I'm a loner, you see.
I'll come with you.
I'D LOVE THAT
EXCLAIMING AGAIN
"Drink water regularly."
That should definitely increase
your daily water intake.
Isn't this cute, too?
Just rub it with your thumb.
It's really soothing.
It's just the right size.
RELAXED
FIDDLING
Shall we get one each? What do you think?
- I'm obsessed.
- Totally.
You like it so much.
- I want the turtle.
- Make it two.
I'll take this one.
SECOND MATCHING ITEM
- Nothing catching your eye?
- I'm actually torn.
- Get this.
- Really?
- That's the one you pick for me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- This one's yours.
- We'll get these here.
- I'd like to pay.
- Thank you.
A LARGE PILE
I didn't mean to get more cups
because I have enough at home.
Just how many did you get?
- Wait.
- I get it now.
I live alone, but I have 15 cups.
Do you buy all the cute cups you see?
That one broke my resolve.
I can skip cute cups,
but not a unique one like that.
It sure is unique. It's one of a kind.
So special.
ALL NEATLY PACKAGED
Could I pay first?
Charles.
- They're on me.
- Thank you.
Thank you, boss.
Well, you don't have to call me that.
I didn't offer to pay
to hear that from you.
No, whoever pays is the boss.
Come on.
It's great getting all the credit
on the company's dime.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
WITH BAGS OF GOODIES
- I'm having so much fun.
- Me too.
ON TO THE THIRD STOP
It really feels
like I'm on Guerrilla Date.
CLUTCHING TIGHTLY
With the whole world watching us.
I'm down with it. I love attention.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I've run before.
- Seriously?
People kept recognizing me,
so I felt self-conscious.
Whenever I hear murmurs of my name
or my agency name,
- I just run away.
- Tell me.
You don't get out much, do you?
No, I just stay at the dorm.
- Here it is. I was here just yesterday.
- "Chaeg Bar"?
Amazing.
CHARLES' FAVORITE PLACE
Here we are. Killer vibes, right?
Nice. I didn't know
there was a place like this.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Hello. Oh, he knows you're a regular.
REGULAR'S PERK
- Hello.
I've visited a bar like this
and fell in love.
MELLOW VIBES
WITH BOOKS TO ENJOY
A PLACE WHERE YOU CAN READ AND DRINK
TO FIND OUT WHAT YOU LIKE
- Do you enjoy reading?
- Well...
- It feels kind of weird to--
- But you enjoy it.
Just say it out loud.
- With confidence.
- I do read. I like it a little bit.
But I get why you're so resistant.
Saying you like reading
can make you sound like a know-it-all.
- Exactly.
- Pretentious, even.
- That's why I couldn't say it.
- I get it.
I regret saying that sometimes.
When I hit the explore page
on social media,
I see posts about the books I recommended.
But the seven books I recommended
were the only ones I read that year.
NO MORE BOOKS TO RECOMMEND
- Want to take a look?
- I'd love that.
Do you like fiction?
I read essays the most and then fiction.
I rarely read essays.
My favorite genre is fiction.
I highly recommend this one.
- Aimez-vous Brahms?
- This one?
It's a classic romance novel.
In summary,
the protagonist is feeling torn
between her long-term boyfriend
and a younger man.
Interesting, right?
- It sure is.
- Try this.
- It's good.
- Okay.
I'll try this one.
Can I make a recommendation?
- Sure.
- It's been adapted into a TV show.
- Hunter With a Scalpel.
- What's the genre?
It's a thriller.
- And they made a TV show?
- That's what I heard.
It's incredible.
I finished it in one sitting.
- Let me write it down.
- Hunter With a Scalpel.
Okay, I'll make sure to read it.
Shall we order some drinks?
They have a fun selection of drinks.
Check this out.
All the cocktails are named after books.
INSPIRED BY BOOKS AND AUTHORS
What should we order?
Let's get a recommendation.
Could you recommend
something fruity and fresh?
Why don't you try "Call Me By Your Name"?
Oh, right.
- It's good. I'll get it.
- So it's sweet and fruity.
- The sky-blue drink?
- Yes.
I'm getting that.
I'll get that, too.
FOLLOWING THE OWNER'S SUGGESTION
- The same ones?
- Yes, please.
You know this place inside and out.
- You must've been here often.
- Here's the funny thing.
I came here yesterday
to have this drink about April.
- The one that had April in its name?
- Right.
The one inspired by a Haruki novella.
I have a thing, you see.
In summer, I read a book
that has "summer" in the title.
- In August--
- You like the themed stuff.
Exactly.
I had to come here in April,
so I even took a cab to get here in time.
But he suddenly asked why I came
when I was coming again the next day.
I was so startled.
I only check the script
on the day of the shoot.
I didn't know
I would be coming here today.
I had no idea we'd be here together.
- So all that was for nothing.
- Yeah, so as it turns out,
- I'm visiting here two days in a row.
- That's nice.
- What did you read yesterday?
- About that.
- All the drinks are book-inspired, right?
- Did you read this?
- I read this over the cocktail.
- A cocktail and a book about April?
That's a perfect combo for April.
- That's my recommendation for you.
- That's fun.
- People eat seasonal food.
- Right.
Just like that,
we can build a seasonal routine.
That gives you something
to look forward to every season.
- You want to figure out your taste.
- I love that.
When you have established
a seasonal routine,
you'll grow to love the seasons more.
That's a good idea.
Can I ask what your life was like at 20?
My life at 20?
How should I put this?
It was a dark time.
WITH UNCLEAR FUTURE
Totally dark?
I was lost back then.
So I don't really have
good memories of that time.
But I believe that time has led me
to where I am now.
VALUABLE EXPERIENCE
That's nice.
What was the first thing
that helped you through it?
Fangirling.
On who?
I was a huge fan of iKON.
Bobby was my bias.
Why am I talking like an idol?
- I didn't know you were in this industry.
- Anyway...
- I was a huge fan of him.
- I know him.
People associate age 20
with new experiences, right?
For me, fangirling was like my first love.
My life was chaos,
but iKON gave me something to hold on to.
They're like your first love.
- Totally.
- Wait,
it sounds like your heart was full.
Why were you lost?
I didn't get into any of the colleges
I applied to.
I ended up going to the one
I didn't want to.
I didn't think I could bear
the stress of CSAT again.
I became really bitter because of college.
- I just--
- Negativity took over?
Yes, it overwhelmed me.
- How sad.
- That phase lasted until I was 23.
- It can be hard to turn it around.
- Actually,
I regained my cheerful self
after starting a YouTube channel.
- Thank you.
- Here are your drinks.
COCKTAILS ARE HERE
REFRESHING COCKTAILS
IN THE SHADE OF THE CLEAR AZURE SKY
CELEBRATING THEIR FIRST MEETING
What about your assignment?
Oh, right.
- We totally forgot about it.
- I know.
"Twenty questions for Wonhee"
for my self-discovery.
"What changed for you after turning 20?"
To be honest...
I mean, I didn't go to college.
Because I'm an idol,
it's just no end of work.
The only thing that has changed
- Just drinks?
- is that I can now drink alcohol.
- Everything else is the same.
- Right, but hear me out.
When you keep thinking
that your life has to change at 20,
you'll only end up disappointed.
I mean it.
Expectations tied to age
are just another social construct.
- I know.
- Right?
"What comment do you get most often
after turning 20?"
"How's being 20?"
- People ask that a lot?
- Yeah.
What was the most memorable comment
you heard as a 20-year-old?
"Make a lot of memories."
"Go on trips."
Especially the one about trips.
But that just made me think,
"Are you paying for my trips?"
"I don't have any money.
How am I supposed to travel?"
Have you been on trips?
Not after I turned 20.
None.
Back when I was in school,
my family traveled together.
We visited Taiwan and Japan
once in a while.
Don't you want to travel?
- I'd love to.
- I see.
- Have you travelled?
- Yeah, multiple times.
Were they therapeutic?
Not exactly, but they leave you
with great memories.
When you look back,
regular days are a blur.
But trips leave you lasting memories,
so you and your friends
can reminisce about it together.
I highly recommend traveling.
Now that you're an adult,
you have more freedom.
- Of course, you're busy,
- Right.
but when you have the time,
travel with your childhood friends.
GO ON AN ADVENTURE
Somewhere close, like Japan.
"What's an ideal adult in your mind?"
It doesn't feel
like you've become an adult.
- No.
- Thought so.
Just legal.
When do you think you'll be a real adult?
At 30.
- Same, so I'm not an adult yet.
- At age 30.
What kind of adult do you want to be?
Well...
I'd like to be someone
who looks good in a black suit
and high heels.
I thought I'd wear heels when I grew up.
Because on TV,
the women are always clicking around
- in heels.
- My thoughts exactly.
But when I wear them,
I walk like a water deer in heels.
Back when I was terrible with heels,
I couldn't walk from the pain,
so my friends supported me.
- Oh, no. Are you flat-footed?
- In the end, I bought cheap slippers.
- I'm not sure.
- I am, actually.
Heels hurt my feet, so I rarely wear them.
"What are the three words
that best describe you?"
I'm not sure who I am as a person.
You've spent a day with me.
Can you pick them for me?
First, you're chill.
- Thanks, I'll write it down.
- And then,
you're highly self-aware.
Highly...
IS SHE A SHRINK?
Highly self-aware.
You're very sensitive
to others' mood changes.
You're the quickest
to notice that about me.
- Really?
- You're the first to catch it so fast.
- How did I seem to you?
- You?
You're so chill.
Let me think.
I was surprised to find... Shoot.
It's such a shame I'm not so articulate.
Did my composure surprise you?
No.
You're more...
THAT WAS QUICK
LEADING QUESTION FAILED
- That's not you.
- Aren't I composed today?
- No, not quite.
- No?
I guess I thought wrong.
- You're very sharp.
- Really?
And you're polite.
Thanks for the compliments.
SATISFIED
"What is your least favorite trait?"
I've got a long list.
Me too.
I don't like that I'm an overthinker.
- Seriously?
- What about you?
I'm far too impatient.
I talk, walk, and eat fast.
I'm so impatient
that slow people frustrate me.
But I get it.
I feel that way sometimes, too.
So I admire people
who move leisurely at their own pace.
I find that very attractive.
- I used to prefer quiet men.
- I see.
COSPLAYING A RELAXED ADULT
Can I ask about your ideal type?
My ideal type?
That's an excellent question.
SUDDENLY MORE ENTHUSIASTIC
- Because--
- I asked so many questions to her,
but I got my first approval now.
SUDDENLY FEELING EMPTY
It's because I've changed my mind
about my ideal type.
Actually, I've openly shared this
so many times.
Who was your ideal type?
It wasn't an individual.
I hoped to meet
a quiet and gentle introvert.
But not these days.
I'd like to meet someone like me.
- Someone outgoing like you?
- Yeah.
I recently had an epiphany.
I'm still attracted to my opposites.
They make my heart race.
- But we just don't click.
- I get it.
I've come to think
that I'd hit it off better
with someone who's like me
than someone who checks every box.
So I've updated my ideal type.
FROM INTROVERT TO EXTROVERT
How would you act
if your dream guy were in front of you?
That's a real challenge for me.
I actually cried a few days ago.
- Why?
- I mean,
all my friends said I acted
like I'd never dated before.
- I also get that a lot.
- The thing is,
I found it so shocking
because I thought
I was so savvy and cunning.
YOU DID, HUH?
I always thought I was such a player.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I don't think of myself like that.
I've never seen someone
who has never dated think that way.
Are you serious?
All my friends asked the same question.
So basically...
Their comments about
how clumsy I am in relationships
made me tear up in the end.
I don't want to be so awkward.
I want to be a pro.
YOU CAN'T LAUGH
I didn't know I was chill
until people told me so.
SPEECHLESS
ZERO SELF-AWARENESS
But you laugh out loud like this.
You don't realize how you look like
when you laugh.
I assumed everyone laughed like me.
Earlier, the production crew told me
I was prettier in person.
- That's so true.
- So I smiled,
but they told me not to smile like that.
Here's the replay.
This is how I smiled.
That was me feeling shy.
That was what I wanted to convey.
I ROLL MY EYES WHEN I FEEL SHY
Your laughs are fine,
but the eye-rolling smile isn't.
Anyway, my point is...
It's hard to know
how other people see you.
CHARLES' SELF-DISCOVERY
You've had a series about dating.
Who did you like best?
SO DIRECT
- Who did you click with the most?
- The most?
No one, actually.
THAT WAS TOO HONEST
Was I too blunt? Let me rephrase.
Everyone was great,
but I didn't feel a spark with anyone.
What's your ideal type?
I don't have a concrete type.
Just...
But trust me, your ideal type evolves
just like your taste does.
Take my case, for example.
My ideal type did a 180
now that I'm a few years older.
Everyone would find
these qualities attractive,
so I'm not sure if it means much.
Basically, I want someone
with a good personality.
A kind person.
But I also want him to be funny.
My ideal guy has to be funny and tactful.
That's about it.
Has anyone acted
so outrageously flirty toward you?
To be honest,
I have very strict standards.
Whoever texts me is a flirt.
JUDGE CHARLES IS A TOUGH ONE
I meant what I said.
"Don't text me if you're not interested."
That's what I want...
That's what I want as my status message.
"Don't text me if you're not interested."
- Let me explain.
- Thank goodness I'm a girl.
A text would make me think,
"Do we have something going on?"
I wouldn't go full delulu,
but I'd wonder if he has feelings for me.
- That's not irrational, right?
- Right.
So even a text counts as flirting.
- So strict.
- But only in cases
where it hasn't been set in stone
that we're only friends.
What if it's for work?
- That's totally okay.
- Right?
How do you define love?
OUT OF THE BLUE?
PHENOMENAL HOSTING SKILLS
I sometimes host a talk show
on my YouTube channel,
and that's one of my signature questions.
Definition of love?
That's so difficult.
To me, it's comfort.
I just don't like friction these days.
- But that's too broad.
- Maybe.
- That'd cover friends, too.
- I love them.
Yes, but my point is...
- Rather than just romantic love,
- The romantic love...
- I'm covering all kinds of love.
- On the whole?
On the whole...
- I'd go with familiarity.
- Familiarity?
- Why?
- I love it.
It's such a good answer.
There's a song about this.
One More Chance released this song,
"I Think of You."
The song goes,
"You chase the thrill of something new.
But I find love in familiarity."
- You didn't know that, did you?
- No.
You should try writing your own lyrics.
"Love is familiarity"? You go, girl.
But it's so easy to forget the close ones.
That's the issue.
- So deep.
- About love...
That comment was gold.
- I'm so inspired.
- Really?
I was worried that sounded cringey.
- Yeah.
- Did your amazing answer weird you out?
- No, it's just that
your reaction caught me off guard.
I should've reined it in.
20-YEAR-OLDS ARE A MYSTERY
Do you ever act cute around people?
Just around people I'm really close with.
The only people I act cute around
are my parents.
I act shamelessly cute around them.
I don't want anyone to see me like that.
Do you go, "Mommy"?
I talk like a baby.
- Wow, really?
- I do that.
How would it feel
to have a daughter like you?
Probably a handful.
NO WAY!
Do you act cute around people?
I'm just like you.
It depends on people.
How are you around your parents?
I'm like a strict eldest son.
- A strict eldest?
- "Mother!"
SO DISCIPLINED
"Father!"
I'm like a drill sergeant.
I speak really softly to my parents.
I act even cuter
when the other person dislikes it.
If they push me away, I act even cuter.
- That makes it fun.
- Exactly.
Seung-heon hates it,
so I act the cutest around him.
I totally get it.
- You overdo it around people like that.
- Yeah.
I even talk with a lisp.
POOR SEUNG-HEON
I lay it on as thick as I can.
I'll tell you the funniest thing
he's ever said to me.
In the end, he went,
"Save this energy
for someone you actually like!"
When I'm around my crush,
- I usually act cool.
- How?
Do you use your drill sergeant voice?
I'm like, "What do you mean?"
I act cold around my crush,
but I act cute around others.
Seung-heon begged me
to do that to my crush.
That's understandable
from his point of view.
What makes you feel loved?
An enthusiastic response.
- Really?
- For instance,
my fans get excited
over the smallest things.
They would go, "My gosh."
When I want my parents
to be worried for me,
- I'd pretend I was getting sick.
- I see.
Their concern makes me feel loved.
- What about you?
- For me,
it's when they take an interest
in my daily life.
I love it. One of my friends
once texted me, "What's up?"
I replied, "Oh, I'm so touched."
STARVED FOR ATTENTION
She was like, "About what?"
The question itself was so touching.
Nobody asks that anymore.
"What's up?" "Thank you."
Trust me. That's the way to my heart.
Just ask me what's up.
AND THAT'S ENOUGH
"If you could get away right now,
where would you go?"
There's only one destination for me.
- Can I guess?
- Hawaii.
I wanted to guess.
Sorry, I got ahead of myself.
The crazy thing is, mine's Hawaii, too.
- I mean it. No cap.
- Seriously?
- For real?
- Sure.
Hawaii is at the top of my list,
- followed by Australia.
- Australia?
My second choice is Okinawa.
Okinawa is so you.
- I mean...
- Are you just going along,
- or are you--
- It suits you.
You're basically Okinawa in human form.
WHAT?
Your clear and fresh image
is a perfect match
for Okinawa's emerald ocean.
I've been compared to the ocean,
but not to a city.
WONHEE, OKINAWA PERSONIFIED
There's a place
I'd like to recommend to you.
Where is it?
It doesn't fit your image per se,
but please visit California.
- Have you been there?
- Yes.
- How was it?
- Just two weeks ago.
- Tell me more.
- I loved it.
I had a fabulous time.
I highly recommend it.
I'll consider it.
I want to see you serving
hot-girl looks over there.
So this is about your curiosity?
You wanted me to go California
to satisfy your curiosity?
- Yes, out of simple curiosity.
- Really?
- Basically,
- It's purely personal.
you just wanted to see me
dressed up like a hot girl?
So that's why you suggested California
out of the blue.
- I want to see your pics.
- I got it.
I hear your goal is to meet
the one within the year.
Oh, right. I wondered how you knew.
I was shocked for a second.
- That's true.
- Have you met him?
I've met many guys,
but I don't know if I've met the one yet.
I've been praying.
RESORTING TO PRAYERS
Does someone particular come to mind?
LET ME JOG YOUR MEMORY
I can't say his name on camera.
So you have someone!
- I do, so--
- Who is it?
You won't know, anyway.
STILL CRAVES THE HOT GOSSIP
You want his name?
Tell me more about him.
Want to know my goal?
- Does this go online in July?
- Yes.
I'd like to be in a relationship by then.
I think you will.
- Fingers crossed.
- I'll be rooting for you.
- Wish me luck.
- Of course.
- "What do you want to hear the most?"
- Me?
What about you?
- Me? "What's up?"
- "What's up?"
"What's up?" "I'm on a shoot with Wonhee."
"Right, you're on a shoot with me.
What else is up?"
It's about my profession.
As a YouTuber,
I open up a huge chunk of my life
to my subscribers.
- So no one asks me for an update.
- It's understandable.
But I want a proper chat.
That's why I feel so happy
when my friends ask me for an update.
- That's my love language.
- I see.
"What's up? I miss you."
From Mr. Mystery, too?
AN UNEXPECTED ATTACK
We're meeting tomorrow.
Here in Mangwon-dong.
Actually, I meant to come here.
- For three days in a row?
- I almost did that.
But the bar closes tomorrow.
It's an off day for the owner.
WILL CHARLES START DATING SOON?
Something you'd like to hear?
For me, "Good luck."
- Really?
- Yeah.
When do you feel down?
I can't think of that,
but I know what energizes me.
I can guess when.
- When you meet fans, right?
- Yes.
- Wait.
- They lift my spirits.
I have a question.
I've never been on stage.
When you see the audience cheer for you,
does that pump you up?
- Sure.
- Really?
- You get pumped.
- Next question.
When you go off-stage,
do you really get an aftershock?
When I come off stage, I feel more like,
- "I did it."
Really?
What are you looking forward to this year?
My group goes on a tour
for the first time.
- Across Asia.
- Really?
- I'd love to go to your concert.
- I'm so excited.
SHY
Really? Please come.
It's our first tour,
so I'm really excited about it.
- You've got this!
- I'll do my best!
GOOD LUCK, WONHEE
That's a wrap on our 20 questions.
Did it help your self-discovery?
Having a talented guide like you with me
and visiting shops across Mangwon-dong
definitely helped.
To be perfectly honest,
you know how too many compliments
can make the other person feel
awkward and uncomfortable.
So I really restrained myself.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I still received so much good energy
from all your compliments.
- Thank you.
- I held myself back.
Just seeing you lifted my spirits.
You know what? Right back at you.
I mean that.
But don't laugh like that.
Why not?
- Wasn't I cute?
- That was cute.
- "Why not?"
- Got it.
Should I do it again?
If someone stops me from laughing,
I'll go, "Why not?"
You're not supposed to close your eyes.
Like this, then?
- Don't roll your eyes.
- Okay.
Got it.
BUMPY ROAD TO ACTING CUTE
- There's a question I ask all my guests.
- What is it?
What's your advice for me?
- It's the final question.
- Advice?
I'd just like to say that you've got this.
I've got this.
I say that for a reason.
As a 20-year-old,
you've got your whole life ahead of you.
I hope you navigate the journey wisely.
- I've got this.
- Good luck.
- Stay strong, too.
- Thank you.
Did I take it too seriously?
- Not at all, it was nice.
- I mean it, though.
- Thank you.
- I'll be cheering you on.
"STAY STRONG THROUGHOUT YOUR JOURNEY"
This is the last episode.
I know.
SAD
LAST ITEM ON THE BUCKET LIST
I also love the water.
WONHEE IS A WATER TYPE
WATER SPORTS ON HANGANG RIVER
GIRLIES FOR THE FINALE
SINB AND DAYOUNG
THEIR ONLY GOAL IS TO MEET WONHEE
Seriously, we're here to see you.
DANCE OF JOY
GIRLIES LOSE THEIR MINDS
WONHEE'S FAN 1
So cute.
WONHEE'S FAN 2
So adorbs.
BOLD DECLARATION
You should teach me.
PRO TIPS FROM HOT GIRLIES
You start from the rizz.
LIKE THIS?
Relax your eyes.
We've got a long way to go.
But you have an aura.
I bet people recognize you easily.
I've got none.
HEART-TO-HEART WITH GIRLIES
CLEARING FINAL BUCKET LIST ITEM
WITH GIRLIES
FEELING FAINT
I feel like throwing up.
SO HAPPY TO BE TOGETHER
LAST ITEM ON WONHEE'S BUCKET LIST
COMING SOON
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim